Guide to the International Graffiti Times archive, 1970-2000.
International Graffiti Times archive
- Series VII. Correspondence
  - Letters from prisons and some military, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Letters from prisons and some military, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11-13)
  - Letters from prisons and some military, 1998-2008 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Letters from prisons and some military, 1987-2008 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Letters, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Letters, 1990-1999 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
  - Writings, letters, interviews, by Vulcan, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12-15)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9-13)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 2-4)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Letters with envelopes, some sent by IGT, 2002-2005 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Letters from Mark Moore, 1989-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Empty envelopes, 1989-2005 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Letters from John Grimes, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - IGT correspondence used in "Now Scream" exhibition, 1989-1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Mail art, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
    Sent to the magazine from artists and institutions including Ryosuke Cohen, Artpool, Vincent Salas and others.
  - Letters and postcards sent to IGT, 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21-22)